ethicalhacker.net 2010-06-21

# 

    The Digital Construction Company (TDCC) Privacy Notice
    Effective May 1, 2008
    
    Privacy Notice Table of Contents: 
    * Our Commitment To Privacy 
    * The Information We Collect 
    * How We Use Information 
    * Our Commitment To Data Security 
    * Our Commitment To Children's Privacy 
    * How To Access Or Correct Your Information 
    * How To Contact Us
    
    * Our Commitment To Privacy 
    
    Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it readily available on our various websites including www.digitalconstructionco.com, www.ethicalhacker.net and www.chicagocon.com. 
    
    * The Information We Collect
    
    The TDCC website is informational only. No information is collected on that site. Therefore, this notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the ChicagoCon or The Ethical Hacker Network websites. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, become a member of the site and register for events. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 
    
    Name
    Organization
    Address 
    Phone Number
    Email address
    
    Payments are handled by PayPal, so no credit card information is collected nor stored internally.
    
    * The Way We Use Information
    
    We use the information you provide about yourself when registering as a member of the given sites or for an event only to complete the registration process. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the registration. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our website if you would like to participate in our discussion forums, receive updates on our news, products and services and special promotions for our events. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above. In order to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses, the user may un-register or send an email to the appropriate site administrator.
    
    * Our Commitment To Data Security 
    
    To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
    
    * Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
    
    Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
    
    * How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
    
    You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by TDCC. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
    
    * How To Contact Us 
    
    Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at info@digitalconstructionco.com.
